# Jorge León Salas

## XR Designer and Developer

jorge.leons@outlook.com

Canada / Vancouver BC

<u>LinkedIn</u>

% Portfolio (WIP)

# PROFILE

I'm a Mexican computer scientist with a diploma on XR design and development.

I love being part of the entire process when it comes to create stuff in order to design solutions that take in consideration every possible point of view. I enjoy trying and developing experiences in game engines in my free time and would like to focus on user experience, such as intuitiveness and accessibility.

# SKILLS

#### 8 / 10

Unity and C#

#### 7 / 10

Unreal Engine and Blueprints

#### 9/10

Teamwork and adaptability

#### 8 / 10

Leadership and assertiveness

#### 7 / 10

HTML, CSS, React, Javascript

# EDUCATION

VR/AR Design and Development Vancouver Film School - 2022

Computer Science Engineering Instituto Tecnologico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey - 2016 – 2020

Videogame design / programming introductory course

Vancouver Film School - 2019

# EXPERIENCE

### Graduate QA Automation Engineer

Solera, Inc / Mexico City, Santa Fe / December 2020 – December 2021

I worked with an internal framework that was mostly based on Selenium and C#. Alongside my manager, we created the first project to use the latest framework, combined with a structure for test cases and great OOP practices, we provided a base project which eliminated the necessity to run the automation project manually and locally, decreased the run time from 3 hours to 30 minutes, added the possibility to schedule runs, and have everything automatically reported to TestRail.

# Digital Innovation & Technology – IT Applications Intern

Schneider Electric / Mexico City, Polanco / September 2019 – June 2020

I mostly developed and maintained web applications. I took part on the development from scratch of a process that eliminated the manual necessity for the annual verification of registered clients.

# PROJECTS

### Pon tu semilla / ITESM, Mexico City / 2019

I was the lead developer for this one-week challenge. I implemented all the VR, Oculus Rift set up for the project and programmed most of the interactions on Unity. I also had to divide the work to be done, and delegate the tasks.

#### DiAppBetes / ITESM, Mexico City / 2019

Swift programmer and XCode operator in an iOS app oriented to inform about diabetes implementing AR Kit to display 360° informational videos and interactive 3D models, biometric identification, and Apple Watch support to track the patient heartbeat.